{
    "id": "ab6ba7fbc3c64e158b8c8cca2a2a4c8f",
    "title": "Verbs worksheet (intermediate level)",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "eb8018166d6a4dd2a24f59426c51fe7a",
            "title": "Intermediate Level Verbs Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "The train …………….. at",
                    "description": "We use the simple present tense to talk about future events that are part of a timetable. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "arrives",
                        "will arrive"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He will meet you when he ………………… back.",
                    "description": "When the verb in the main clause is in the simple future tense, we use a present tense in the subordinate clause to refer to the future. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "come",
                        "comes",
                        "will come"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "When I got home, my dog ………………. at the gate waiting for me.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "sits",
                        "sat",
                        "was sitting"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ……………….. Gupta this evening.",
                    "description": "If the arrangement already exists, we use the present continuous tense to talk about future. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "visit",
                        "will visit",
                        "am visiting"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Look at the sky. It ………………….. to rain.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "is going",
                        "goes",
                        "is"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The train ………………… before we reach the station.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "will arrive",
                        "would arrive",
                        "will have arrived"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Perhaps we ………………. Singapore next month.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "visit",
                        "will visit",
                        "are visiting"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The next term ………………. on Monday.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "begin",
                        "begins",
                        "will begin"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Oh dear! I …………………",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "will die",
                        "am dying",
                        "die"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I’m sure she ……………….. the job.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "gets",
                        "will get",
                        "would get"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}